Arima Kobayashi

FULL STACK ENGINNER

□ arimakobayashi6@gmail.com

Nagoya, Japan

Summary

As a Senior Full Stack Engineer with 8+ years of experience, I have a passion for great software product, user friendly interfaces and good user experience. I consider myself a fast-learner, self-challenger, and problem-solver. What I bring to your project is making sure your website generates more leads, customers, and revenue. I have built 4+ projects from the ground up, and strong experience in an agile environment taking initiative and shipping products while contributing to collaborative design, engineering and product team. I am highly skilled in a variety of platforms, development frameworks and programming languages, and can easily adapt to new platforms and services. I take pride in writing code that is well-documented and designed. I have been focusing on designing and implementing full-stack applications using advanced web/mobile technologies.

Experience

Full Stack Engineer

Feb 2022 - Present

TWIN SUN / Remote / Nashville, Tennessee, USA

- · Provided analysis of software, code, requirements, metrics, and risk for projects assigned
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues
- Planned website development, converting mock-ups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, React, Vue, Nuxt and web components
- Created e-commerce sites integrated with PayPal, Authorize.net and other payment API using React, Node.js and PostgreSQL
- Crafted SEO strategy and intuitive interface for site to achieve prominent rankings across top browser platforms with Next.js
- Conducted unit testing to deliver optimal browser function ality using Jest, Cypress, Mocha, and Chai

Full Stack Engineer

Sep 2019 - Jan 2022

Rakuten / Hybrid / Tokyo, Japan

- Created a new ecommerce platform from the ground up, including designing and developing all aspects of the website
- Worked with management to create an ecommerce strategy that included SEO best practices for increased traffic
- Developed a custom shopping cart system using PHP/MySQL and JavaScript frameworks like ReactJS and AngularJS
- Improved site speed by optimizing images, reducing HTTP requests and compressing CSS/HTML files
- Collaborated with marketing team on product descriptions, landing pages and copywriting for email campaigns

Python Enginner

PARTY / Hybrid / Shibuya City, Japan

- Implemented integration with deep learning results and backend endpoints
- Implemented front-end E2E testing and unit testing with Cypress, Jest, Mocha, and Chai
- Built a data management system that can handle large amounts of data, scrapping, visualization, and modeling
- Implemented front-end features that can visualize large amounts of data with D3.js, chart.js, and other JavaScript libraries
- Experienced in large amounts of data handling using Python libraries such as Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn

Front End Engineer

May 2015 - Feb 2017

XOXZO / Onsite / Taito City, Japan

- Planned and engineered RESTful web services to manipulate dynamic datasets using Laravel
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed using Next.js
- Developed user-friendly website, including optimized check-out page that increased user clicks, and subsequently customer purchased by 20% using ReactJS

Education

Nagoya University

Bachelor of Computer Science

2011 - 2015

Skills

- TypeScript / JavaScript / Python / PHP
- React / React Native / Next.js / Svelte
- Remix / Redux
- Vue.js / Nuxt.js
- Node.js / ExpressJS / Nest.js
- Django / FastAPI / Flask
- Cypress / Jest / Mocha / Chai

- REST API / GraphQL
- MySQL/MongoDB/PostgreSQL
- Docker/Docker Composer
- AWS / Azure
- Ngnix / Apache
- Git / GitHub / Gitlab / Bitbucket